for all those boats to shake
Well, what makes me feel calm is that no
I am the only one who guides him and he knows it
I am calm knowing that he knows it
The other day in a video I said that I hated
Adam Sandler and many asked me about
So here I am answering you for that today.
among them I summarize without further ado because I hate
Adam Sandler a couple of years ago was in
a long distance bus and they put one
movie are like children two like the
options were to look at that or look at the route
through the window I chose to see that
film started with Adam Sandler
sleeping and when he wakes up there is a
I close the side of the bed that is put in
two legs and a lemme in the mouth
[Music]
and I wondered why it started like this
movie who came up with that
joke then I thought I don't understand it
because it must be a code that comes from
1 then a couple of days later in
vila one alone to understand that joke and
What a surprise I got when I saw that no
There was not a single joke about servants or
a
I'm not surprised then by that joke.
had not the slightest [ __ ] sense when the
screenwriters of the film who are Adam
Sandler and his buddies founded
write the script someone said that the
film think with a closure surrounding
the protagonist mouth and everything they said to be
and the movie are like children 1 and 2 are
just because
at one point a guy stands up
from an ice cream machine just so that
the shin matches the ass and when
chocolate ice cream comes out look like [ __ ]
because if at another time one gets involved
inside a tractor wheel and goes
going around the whole town because
if the movie is pure jokes
jokes about adults doing stupid things
adult jokes seeing her tits there were
younger jokes about people hitting each other
hello
or not
probably dog jokes
[Applause]
[Music]
and
to all the random jokes that are told
were happening at the last moment
They joined together with a plot that no one
the problem with humor matters
Sanders is not that he challenges himself to do so
The problem is that it's comfortable humor
for example in one part they throw a
arrow up because yes and when
They run away, one trips and falls
face against a mountain of poop
because if nobody thought that joke more than
two seconds and you can make that joke
kill anywhere in the movie
in any Adam Sandler movie and goes
to be exactly the same
I'm going to compare it to another joke.
fall that if all the males are good
must take a leap of faith if he survives
on this 6-story jump will try 2
that has this character performs this
message
[Laughs]
because this joke is funny and this
another one is not cool because this one has three
first shot the fall that was going to happen
be false but by pure bad luck it was
true second auction the fall is
very long third auction the honesty and
innocence or mere confession that he is
the bandage fell off and you have to do the
try the Simpsons joke again
it is thought this is not thought
They said that you trip and fall
on top of a mountain of [ __ ]
then Adam Sandler's falls more
which jokes would be just bloopers
American bloopers
[Music]
and that's how almost all of his films are.
It's my top five movies that I hate the most.
From Adam Sandler to Creation I didn't see them
I only speak of those who are civil.
5 clicks
I never made sense of this
film teenage life and everything
time I wondered why why and
why and why is Christopher
walken there are 44 are like children 1 in
compared to their schools this is the
godfather position 3 a fake wife and
murder mystery because they are bad and why
He dragged Jennifer Aniston into this.
all declared them husband and Larry a
A movie called that can't be
good never put 1 they are like children 2
special mention I didn't see Jack and Jill
But yes, one Adam Sandler bothers me.
imagine 2 but before continuing
explaining why the audio I'm going to
answer the big question of where it comes from
Adam Sandler made his acting debut in
the Bill Cosby series in 1988
and then starred in a very
rare that is called voice over ball where
speaks to the camera
after that it started to be standard
Even with such Dennis Miller he saw it and
He brought that 'talde' to Saturday Night Live
In Milan he is responsible for everything.
The culprit without Dennis Miller there is no
Adam Sandler then appeared in
movies like Hell's Angels and its
first leading role vile and madison where
his humor was going to be defined a bit
adult doing stupid things dnm that's it
the basis of Adam Sandler's humor and another
thing that has been defined with that
film about his relationship with critics and
the box office because the critics made it
[ __ ] but he lifted a bag of hita and
To make movies it doesn't matter what you say
was heard boredom Catalina dlugi lo
What matters is what the box office says
For example, a cool dad cost 34
million dollars and raised 234
A fake wife cost 48 million
millions and raised 215 million click
It cost 82 million and raised 237 million
a child cost 80 million if that [ __ ]
It cost that money where is one of the
movies is where that money is
imports and together 271 million or the
guy is a success even though everyone
Say you don't like Adam Sandler
majority lies because those numbers are not
do alone I continue doing many
films hated by critics but
loved by the public founded her own
producer and made a small group of
friends who amuse me less than him
and they are rob schneider like the one who
always makes exotic characters that do not
have nothing to do with the plot of the
baby movie saying goodbye like the one who does
always a bachelor who has sex with more women
younger than him
kevin james always seems to do the
joke with what game and just joke
So Nick Swardson is as fat as he is.
who jokes that he is clumsy and that
I know that the floor and those things that win me
want better known as font de happy
day' as the case always since old
because the old man and the participation
special witnesses in and as the best
actor Adam Sandler worked with
sometime in his life but always
they can do stupid things
But what I hate about Adam Sandler is not
his [ __ ] movies that I don't like
not at all but well he doesn't do them with me
money is not made with state money
pays for them and what's your problem?
Also, humor is the most subjective self that
there is no such thing as what can cause me
thanks to another no and vice versa and I can't
say that Adam Sandler's movies
They are bad because millions and millions
of people like them and shit on them
laughter for example when Adam Sandler
made them like children, two made it so that
people laugh and the goal was
fulfilled never sought to be praised by the
criticism I don't think I've said it seems to me
Since they are like children, they won me the Oscar.
I'm not trying to make people laugh in the original script.
with jokes [ __ ] and we did it
What I heard from Adam Sandler is that moving forward
deprives us of Adam Sandler there are certain
movies that showed me that the type
He is a very good actor as Spanglish by
example or to mediate with the story one of
The best films of 2017 and one day
vi su show de stand up en netflix y me
I laughed a lot and it was a genuine laugh.
with Adam Sandler and not from Adam Sandler
then I realized that the guy is
good actor is funny but chooses the
comfortable humor the humor of farting
and it's not that I hate peso jokes
but there are fart jokes and jokes about
dogs a good fart boy is the DT
what's the difference the fart is funny
just for being a fart
[Laughs]
But here is a guy who did badly in
a date and the only good thing that came out of it
All that was able to lengthen that hair
that I was holding on and that is something that
Surely that happened to us of not being able to
tirarnos un pedo porque estamos con
people and when we are finally alone
make the fart is the joke and here the fart
It's the punchline of the joke, but oh well
nor to analyze a joke so much
farts but to be fair it ends my top
five movies that I do like
Adam Sandler ranked 5 a great dad
I saw a lot of the boy and I grew fond of him.
[Music]
well every time nothing
450 first dates is quite a lot
good and has original jokes
put three madmen of rage make me king of
true and makes a good duo with Jack
nicholson
dead 2 spanglish is spoken of this
film ranked 1st in the media with acts
very good and ben stiller is there too
hell
Conclusion I hate Adam Sandler because
being able to make quality humor chooses
make comfortable humor and easy jokes
and he also saw it because he dragged him to
Steve Buscemi there are people who believe that he is
a stupid old man
and no no no
is one of the best and most
underrated actors of the world and now
I want to know what you think, you hate him.
Adam Sandler loves him, what is their bond like?
with it leave it written in the
good comments
In 1973, Roberto Gómez Bolaños created a
program about a group of people who
I lived in a neighborhood and against everything
forecast was a success a success of the
great flute both in Mexico and in
Latin America as well as in several countries
rest of the world the cast was in its
best moment and it seemed that everything
was going relatively well but in
In reality, everything was going relatively badly.
because the actors got along worse than
their characters which led to one of
They will leave the show at no.
1978 saw the premiere of the magnanimous chapter of
Acapulco and although at that time it was not known
I knew in the last chapter where
Kiko would appear that year Kiko left the
'El Chavo del Ocho Show' and that would be the one
beginning of the end the beginning of the
Chao's decadence full of judgments
dismissals, plagiarism, betrayals of
aging and plots clinging to the
hairs that's why today I summarize them if
also the decline of Chao
[Music]
in the neighborhood still without Kiko until
They made a half-simple excuse with their
The rich godmother, I no longer remembered if
She couldn't live with all this anymore.
mob and everything continued as if nothing had happened and Mrs.
Florinda never spoke of her again.
son which made her more violent than
that it was already and I warn you of one thing I am going to
killing is like steps to your luxurious dog
to take the place that Kiko said
They began to give more prominence to the party
year
apophis and I make money
you were not what
how is it that you are accusing me of anything
Thanks and other than that everything is normal.
Normal but with less quality they continued
with the hysterical giraffe bidders
with Doña Florinda, the one from Don Ramón with the
witch and the problem of the bulls and the
The boy made his bag worse because of the
poor nutrition FAO
[Music]
and obviously they continued with the same
humor to hit yourself
become dirty
the water
and every now and then some good joke that
when I gave it back to do the
video I'm going to laugh
I'm not going to put something that is very
important at parties to put
enthusiasm, a lot of enthusiasm
apparently everyone was happy
everyone except one person himself
Carlos Villagrán because with the departure
Kiko's legal battle began and
Therefore, more battle of Mexico
Carlos Villagrán gives his Roberto Gómez
Bolaños and the objective of the dispute was the
character team
Carlos Villagrán is playing the program
for reasons that were never fully understood
clarify the last thing he said
publicly is that Chespirito lowered them
because Kiko was becoming more
popular 70 percent of the
questions were for boy because he was
fashionable because not but it's your ball
practice of paw then began to
awaken a little envy
selfishness, professional zeal, that's it
artistic which brings me to the big question
ask who is the favorite of the
people
Kiko or Chavo leave your vote in the
comments we hydrate so hold with
endurance
and since they were in the area of the
comments put a subscribe to the channel
and metal already a click on the bell of
know if it works I think it does
It works and also follow Acquarone Bar
who made the nice intro of El Chavo Man
men and also I made a nice one
collaboration on your channel so I
I leave the link in the description but
Well, going back, the thing is that Carlos
Villagrán said, "Jewel, I'm leaving, but"
I want to continue playing my character in
on the other hand, what Chespirito told him
that your character is small in my opinion
character I invented it, it's not mine
character said Carlos Villagrán Jolie
mind and so they went to trial and the truth
the truth is not clear who had
reason does not matter because what does remain
Of course, Chespirito was more powerful.
and more millionaire and he won the trial
I'm not surprised when you end up mijarán
The owner of the channel leaves the kid
He got so angry that he sent them a letter to
all Latin American channels
threatening them that if they gave him
work to Carlos Villagrán he decided to
to remove the broadcasting rights from the
Chavo and of all the soap operas two are
[ __ ] up to the legs and ignored him
here with all the channels
Latin America closed its doors to him
except for a Venezuelan channel here he gave it
work and let him do four programs
one worse than the other and always with a
character like kiko but instead of
Kiko with ass had to write with here
for rights began with the child of
paper where he played a character
suspiciously similar to boy
[Applause]
and then he continued with Federico where he has
been a suspiciously character
similar to kiko and there was a character
suspiciously similar to Doña Florinda
and a suspiciously similar character
the boy has a character
suspiciously similar to Don Ramón ah
not for now it's don ramón good that you
I'll explain later what followed was a
program that was called kiko botones where
he played a suspiciously character
similar to kiko but who worked as
bellboy at a hotel and then did another
that was called there is that kiko where
played a character similar to
Federico who in turn in the
suspiciously similar to kiko there
there would be another character and Huelva the boy
The thing is that Kiko spent his life
doing double acts of Kiko and
fighting over the character with Chespirito
until finally in 2013 he said
enough up to here and he retired and stopped
act forever but returning the
Boy, if you thought that Kiko's departure
It was the worst thing that could happen to him
program is wrong is wrong badly
already in the era without Kiko they were made
very unmemorable chapters like the
who go to the cinema because they don't come back
indecent
Hector Bonilla visits if the very same
export bonilla or the one that doña clotilde
has a dog named Satan
year you haven't seen Satan around here
and several in the arithmetic school
our god and geometry neither and we
It took a month to pass from the departure of
Kiko that the cast was already suffering
another loss a very important loss
nail that finishes closing the coffin
early 80s he left nothing more
Nothing less and nothing more than Don Ramón
[Applause]
If Don Ramón himself, my character
Ramón's favorite is by far my favorite
favorite because when you go you leave it in
evidence that he was the center of the
The series without Don Ramón had almost nothing left.
sense to whom Doña Florinda hits
who was chasing the witch who was chasing him
Mr. Belly collected the rent, who
He looked after the chilindrina with whom he
the boy fought, everyone had a bond
particular with Don Ramón he was
really the soul of the series
reasons for his departure were also
confusing and there were always several
versions the last one that exists is the one of
brother of Ramón Valdez who says that he
It was because Doña Florinda had begun to
direct and Don Ramón did not have much room for it
that a woman is in charge and
Ramón was right with and hey but how
new one went to the [ __ ] and where did she go
He left with Kiko the greatest tradition
of all the traditions or was that one
spirit the traitor who stole the
character quico to this uncertainty of
not knowing what happened makes me feel bad
I don't know who is evil and wants to be good
The thing is that to justify that the
Chilindrina will continue to live in the
neighborhood was given more importance today
Nieves the great-grandmother
my great-grandmother
[Music]
and as the characters leave but the
jokes didn't have to invent something
to continue with the Lord's little gems
belly collecting the rent then
a mysterious inn appears owned
Mr. Belly and attended by a
listless subject I want you to make me
Please bring us some tacos to the table
same distance from here to there as from
from here to there
suddenly without much justification, madam
Florinda decides to buy it this time.
Mrs. Florinda
you should open a restaurant
thoroughly and suddenly they start to
spend adventures at the inn
Doña Florinda if you want to know the
Doña Florinda restaurant, don't forget to visit
watch the next program on this channel
and at the same time and as all this was not
enough to cover the pothole left
Ramón invented a new character
I am the new postman and what is my fault?
I have come, Jaimito, I am from
tangamandapio as the thing did not have nor
chances to improve and spirit decided
stop making entire chapters of
half an hour to turn the kid into
shortest sketches included in a program
called Chespirito where there was more
characters by Roberto Gómez Bolaños and
With this decision, the process now begins
decline of struggle
without Kiko, without Don Ramón and with fragments
Shorter the thing had no return to
To this we must add that the actors
They began to age and in addition to
having old and ridiculous people dressed up
Like children, it seemed they had no desire
to move and the chapters began to
return very static like this where
they play cards
[Music]
or this one where they talk about the Red Cross
we may all need it at some point
We must help, yes, but of all these
bad chapters there is one that is the worst
of all one who had all the
win but lost the crossover of the chavo
and the red grasshopper'
[Music]
It seems that everyone was in the neighborhood
in a bad mood then the boy invokes the
'red grasshopper' so that it is solved
this and I don't know if it's because they were
old or because this spirit acting
alone or because there is no laughter in the background anymore
but the scenes don't have a bit of
rhythm follow me the good ones
ah
put willpower into your mother's cunt
put your will into it but the worst thing is the worst of it
everything is the way they found to
that the grasshopper takes away his bad mood a little
Chavo asked me to help you
You've already got your good mood back.
Thank you golden public, you came back
good course
Of course, better than ever
Of course, because the show is in a good mood
del chavo became controversial in the
They are sitting in the bar talking very badly
maybe in a moment he'll use the pill
Chiquitolina did not count on my cunning
and maybe after this I would have to
summarize the 'chapulín colorado' so no
I'm running out, I like it if you're in agreement
I agree with this I say but in addition to
to make bad chapters they resorted to
old and reliable recycled chapters
like the gum in the hat but
now in the bag
[Applause]
I chose the wrong bag because I chose the wrong one.
Don't worry about the hat, it's in your
hands make mistakes
It is human
smallpox returns, everyone had theirs
beautiful redheads
[Music]
of Catalan laughter
ah
They did the neighbor's like 40 times
new
for my soul
[Music]
I am
To be fair, I'll highlight the only one
good moment of this saga of the boy in
a chapter seems that Don Ramón makes
a special participation returning to
the neighborhood and supposedly the actress
that made the chilindrina not know that
came back and supposedly his reaction
[Music]
place
be true not much with egg is a
very nice and very emotional scene
finally in the early 90s almost
12 years later the Chavo show had
a final chapter that wasn't even
final end because they didn't know that it was
It ended there but it was the last thing that
He saw the boy and said, "Explain to me why."
If she does that, she's a swine.
a joke that was repeated 20 times that
metaphor after the chavo each one
He continued with his life as best he could
trying to live in a world where already
They are in Castile tenths with their
characters and it is very difficult to do something
new
Chespirito continued hitting him hard and evenly
Bye because he made an animated series
where everyone is except Chilindrina
the only one who was able to win a trial against
Chespirito and Señor with character 18
spirit until November 28
of 2014 died and although he died his
legacy is more alive than ever because
Although almost 50 years have passed
its premiere in the chapters are followed
happening in almost every country in
Latin America and luckily they pass by
Well, not the old ones, the Chavo show
the television series that taught us that
you have to say enough at your best
and not when he is already old and has fought with
everyone and without ideas tremendous moral
Well
good night
[Applause]
today among the summary just like that doctor
House is the story of a doctor in
reality of a super doctor he is a
expert in all specialties of
Medicine knows all the
diseases of the world and history
and I diagnose you just by looking at you and
I also know that he is lame and is in charge of the
diagnostic department and only treats
with impossible rare diseases
unlikely diseases that no other
doctor of the universe can diagnose
except House, who diagnosed everyone
works with a team made up of
three other doctors and although they have
changed over the seasons
It will always be respected that they are from
different shapes and colors so you can
refer to them without needing to know
the names of the first team formed
for the blond, the black man and the pretty one
second team the Jew the Indian and the
Linda and the third team the Jewish one
China and the cute house also has a
best friend named wilson and is
oncologist and also has a friend who
Her name is Cody and she is the director of the hospital.
and even though he is never wrong
she will oppose chapter chapters to her
crazy treatment if ever
will have to house is the thickest of the
world in the first chapter comes a
patient with a disease but house
He is not interested in treating her until
a symptom appears that calls it
attention after test three
different diagnoses until
finally due to an external situation the
main single box in the tab and
discover the real problem of your
patient the cure and end of that episode
It was the first chapter and so will be the ones
another 177 but they are changing
patients every now and then something happens that
makes one think that the series is going to take another
course like when house kills without
love Wilson's girlfriend and they
They fight and we say that's fine
Now new things are going to happen but
right away, friends, and everything goes bang bang bang bang.
continue as always or as when caused
for having hallucinations end a
neuropsychiatric and we say that
Well now new things are going to happen
but the other chapter read the discharge of the
hospital and bang bang bang everything continues as before
always in another season house is put
boyfriend with this one but she leaves him and
house in come to throw is the car in
the house
Jaua prisoner and we say that's good
Now new things are going to happen
but the other chapter is free again
to the hospital and boom boom everything continues
as usual
This is how we learn that house is
trapped in a cyclical and imprisoned universe
hard imperturbable routine where it goes
the week should have patients with
rare diseases diagnose them
bad three or four times to have one
anagnorisis and finally cure them but
Everything has an end and this series too
In the last chapter, House dies in a
accident from which he could not survive
no human being but in the last
scene we find out that in reality
caused his death as very easy and did it
to share with Wilson his last
months because he has cancer but not
It matters and with this beautiful image
will end if well this was eight
seasons of the house thrush
people like technologies
long in quilombos you feel in the water
you feel it on the ground, you smell the air
and it is read in the numerous requests that
We are with the fairies and the renewal has already been made.
I work with swords and magic, that's why
May the Lord of the world serve us today
Rings' Part 1 The Fellowship of the Ring
It's a hole in New Zealand and a hobbit hole.
that is, a dress with legs
hairy but canellis not this small
bourgeois who calls himself red receives from his
uncle a ring that looks like you have
invisible actually happens to you for the
dark side
It happens that this is the valued ring of a
bad which is evil personified
although they defeated him long ago and now
It is an eye of fire that in a tower
dark next to a volcano in the middle
from a country full of horrible bugs
that are invading every issue that
Its only weak point is the ring and
Frodo has to go halfway around the world
distance threw the volcano to tear it out
to do in this adventure what
other conspirators accompany them and they
They are channels that before leading a
group of mutants was a baa1 magician
Orlando Bloom who before directing until
Taking the east, the Caribbean was the most important focus
Middle-earth Levant
Charly that before taking down the queen of
and ends with a young man who is sent
shits and another fat young man
and before helping in the matter he came to
play these people must be in addition to
be the character who doesn't make it to the second
part series is the character who does not arrive
to the second part of this film
Mortensen who, in addition to being Susana's friend
He is a friend of these people but many more
They want to take off the ring first some
black guys who are given to us
get rid of the daughter
with this
and here is Viggo Mortensen's girlfriend and
Agent Smith's daughter who after
so much doing bad now he does good
and there is also Christopher Lee another one
magician that Magnetto is going to ask for help
but since he didn't even see Star Wars and
Charlie and the Chocolate Factory no
He knows that he is actually very bad
and help me we are making balls of
mouse back the group is walking and
walking with a lot of other landscapes and
many beautiful people like Kate Blanchett
who, true to his custom, makes a queen
Here she is the queen of the elves but at
In the end, the bad guys catch up with them by luck
Flood and his bodyguards had
erased in time with the ring
charly in other hobbits are taken
prisoners and Viggo Mortensen with
Orlando Bloom and the Dwarf instead of going
with the protagonist they send you to look for
the less important hobbits and don't you
I answer on the way they meet
a giant demon and gandalf saving the
rest of the web
as
the agreement accompanies you magneto and so with
the scattered boys finish the
first part but it goes on and on with the
Part 2: The Two Towers, but day of the
fat man meets the best
character from the saga flew here in the
Frodo's shot ever took out the
ring and now the team is back
media that make a deal so that the
go straight to the volcano even if it is enchanted
that the goal is going to [ __ ]
and sources
i
look so much a few opportune riders kill
the monsters and hobbits stay
with a gentleman with a face has turned around
through the forest and his friends following us
up close you find nothing else and
nothing less and nothing more than Magneto
resurrected now promoted to white mage
together they go to the kingdom of the riders
put a pick to enter the endurance
Here the plot sort of stops for a while
attempted love triangle where one
blonde wants to get up to Vigo but he
He already has his eye on the Moor
with this
but then things get good
bad neither slow nor lazy they armed
high army the defense is weak if
The boys resist as best they can in a
battle saved that seems impossible
win until reinforcements arrive and
warren with the enemies to the [ __ ] so
With a momentary victory we move on to
Part 3: The Return of Gaia
the winning girl meets in the
Christopher Lee's Ranch where first
a botched job before he is locked up but
In the expanded version we alternate that
dies painfully no more in the
the most indisputably good kingdom
white city is worth the white magician with a
white horse comes to warn them of a
imminent attack of the blacks
Dr. Wilson receives and here is the
father of the deceased, needy and caregiver
of the throne but does not get along very well with
Magnetto and now everything is possible because
the command army comes the smoke
defense is weak and the boys
assist as best they can in a battle
a save that seems impossible to win
until reinforcements arrive and beat
with the enemies at [ __ ] again
Viggo Mortensen who, along with all the
that there are left for one last battle
same doors of the PD the bad guys while
so much made the hobbits important
a turn is in this but as it was obvious
that giant spider bill of about
a few more meters and they reach the volcano
where Frod almost screwed up trying to
stay where there are rings but for
luck brings goal even if unintentionally
wanting to take it out and it will fall lava with
Their prices and everything and volume are up to
then the madman tower the army and
the entire territory of the country of the
bad as it should always be good
until the last moment always
celebrated Viggo Mortesen and crowned him king
and marries Steven Tyler's daughter
with this
and after seeing how everything is at home
but his uncle Magnetto and many nice people
more people take the bus than a kind of
paradise that they never show us
we assume that everyone beyond or you are going to
stay and happily ever after as
This was Lord of the Rings
summarized but more if we get to the skin some
day we will summarize the young and if point
Exactly dry for and film the Lyon sinkhole
[Music]
Welcome to the Tom Hanks multiverse
a multiverse full of lands
alternatives where we will see a tom
hanks military a tom hanks russo
lost in a terminal to a Tom Hanks
astronaut to a tom hanks sending emails
to a tom hanks in love with a mermaid and
much more on twitter sorry about which ones
They are the three Tom Hanks in which
should start in this first video and
They chose Tom Hanks who runs Tom
hanks now pro voy al tom hanks
jailer the next wants to vote
follow me on twitter because I have twitter
Now hold on to your sister-in-law because we're going
to start a journey through the muddy multi
by Tom Hanks and things start in the
Tom Hanks's Earth 28 will be called
forefore gama
the story of forest gump a little boy who
He was born with a problem in his legs
then they put some irons in it to
that he walks until one day some whistles
They were not left with stones today he came out
running well to coordinate lost the
carts and so he began to use his paw
rather unnecessarily, that is, the irons
the video always with the mother and father
and this generated a great Oedipus complex
flute and spends all day talking about it
thousand
pain in the ass for the big corpse of
your old man a little and things get more
rare the day that stays in the yard
listening to the mother march with him
school director and it gets even more
strange when you find out that he was there
in love with the mother on earth 17
but that doesn't matter what matters that
She throws him the phrase that marked him the most
more so it is like an irony because it has
multiple skills such as running
run with people in your arms, run faster
with car run faster with a
explosion or was it American football giving
good answers in the army arm
a rifle in record time to be a field
ping pong being a field of the
industry shrimp cut the grass
I salute the president, mortal ass
president of this for compilations
nationals and teach dance but he has
a weakness because running small
met the love of his life
and
recognized were the butter and it was
the boy
and they were
what started out as a beautiful friendship
As adults it became an obsession
for her he is obsessed with whether she is
all the time thinking about her and
talking about her didn't let her have it
other couples helped her without her
I asked him to imagine when he didn't
He was described as putting 500 letters on it
his name a ship a psychopath knife
and he took advantage of that and you repelled him
I was already with him, he sent her but I have
been able to search but Paul abandoned but
then I looked for it again but it
rejects it but then it goes but then it goes
abandon again and forensic that they do
your generic shell face of
I turned around and the latter abandoned me
Forest Gump is already getting hairy and
I caught the knock on the corral but but but
here you are going to go to the [ __ ] and you are going to run
throughout the USA for three long years and
suddenly stops running but life
de forest do not turn all the only two
female figures who in their lives did not
do many things at a time, it gets involved
the hill and meet the second best
character from the movie bubas and later
meet the best character in the movie
Lieutenant Dan, whom Tom Hanks calls
would meet again on earth 176
vending premium
[Music]
but the thing is that now it is missing
Vietnam War and everything starts to
go relatively well until
begins to march relatively like the
very [ __ ] same because they attack them
[Music]
new death
and it is true that Cuba dies because of Cuba
May the force be with you
The news is that the lieutenant has
survived the good news is that
lose your legs daily forest winning
and keeps his promise grape and bought a
shrimp boat to catch shrimp and
as in this world everyone fulfills their
promises lieutenant dan is going to
working with forest and at first they
It goes like the [ __ ] but after
singing to God has a super storm
They start to do well and become
really millionaires but bad things come
news
So Forest goes with his mother and here
One of the saddest scenes is coming
of the world the first scene of a
movie that made me cry the death of
Mrs. Gum
Tell me if you are crying too
I'm sure it is but I told him it's forensic
a roller coaster and just as they arrive
Bad news comes to you, good news because
He receives a letter from Jenny and it was armed
there he meets Jenny and
have breakfast with someone who has a order and they support
and proposes marriage to her and Forest Gump in
instead of wondering if my son will be next
He's hooking me up and asking for another stoner
The only proof I have is my son
is that we both turn our heads to the
same side only instead of
wondering all that accepts the touch
and also tells him that he is going to die
quote well what is it that they don't understand and
They get married and now I ask them
You, the sheep that will be the son of
couples who have an opinion leave your vote in the
comments go to my install that I made
a survey to end this
mystery of a good time that happened look
the one-minute summaries I made this
movie to see the movie could have
had ends with marriage but not
for life to flourish is a pain and
Jenny obviously dies and to underline
plus Forest Gump's Oedipus dies in the
same bed where the mother died
He dies and the coroner is left neglected
They ask him and he sits there while
the pen he found at the beginning is gone
flying but this is not the only link
Something else happened to Tom Hanks with the sea.
grave on land 89 with camps has a
plane crash and ends up lost
in the sea but before that it is a
very important executive of FedEx PP
expert express but by far it is always
I feel like sending something by
faith of the thing that is perhaps with Helen
hunt and one day he goes on a trip and tells
senegal
but the [ __ ] is not coming back soon nor
in a pickle because I get into an accident like that
Tom Hanks is stranded on an island and
the only thing he has to eat and drink
There are a few who are also their
worst enemies with which he is going to
have a fierce battle for
open them
[Music]
Diaz and Tom Hanks discover the knife and
How can Juan not take the coconut?
discover the bottle when it is given
realize that they are not going to rescue him, he begins
to adapt to life in the jungle and
Thanks to this beautiful montage you learn to
survive
and Tom Hanks discovers fire
Fortunately for the ex and him
a lot of objects appear that
There were some of the HC on the plane
skates and a nice dress with which
Discover net fishing but so camps
also discover your feet because by
a romanticism [ __ ] that is not
understand decide not to open that box and
There was food and there was a radio
smooth satellite and a pillow I don't know what
If I could see anything that you
It works, but for now, what's in that box?
It's a question you'll never get
answer is clear there is point but in
There's a ball in those FedEx boxes.
Wilson and Tom Hanks create life
and so wilson was born and tom hanks discovers
schizophrenia and also discovers the
dentistry and also discovers the
ellipsis
Four years is a long time for a
ellipsis arch how it adapted to the jungle
how he learned to fish and how it was
day he wanted to kill himself that he did those
four years because the director decided
demonstrate bully jan [ __ ] but not
doing things in three or four years in
red these are questions that never
They will get answers, it is clear.
play point the thing is that one day tom
Hanks discovers sailing
then he decides to build a nice raft
adjusting the things you have on hand
[Music]
then lisa wilson wilson with this
raft we are going to save ourselves and wilson is not
He thinks it's all nonsense
The raft is going well and is entering the
high seas and much the [ __ ] is that Wilson
the water falls and you never get back
give another loss to take
Well
there was a rescued lumbar cole and
ellipsis and another longer one then look how
Wilson looks at you, it seems to me that you are
abusing the ellipsis in short Tom Hanks
He meets Helen Hunt again but she
She is very famous because she got married and had a
daughter and Tom Hanks is left with a face like that
[ __ ] mother everything goes wrong for me in this
The Belgian film also goes with Don
hahn being that package previous
[ __ ] that never opened and so meets the
owner of the package and well the story
It remains open and has no end to it.
Someone get me out of this situation
uncomfortable please
[Music]
dance this summary ends with the
Universe 138 aka Tom Hanks is an old man.
who starts to cry seeing in the
movie and an old woman asks him why
You cry Tom Hanks, I'll tell you about it.
that tone sings I'm going to tell a story
very long and full of details that do not
It is important to accommodate UGT because this is going to happen
for long and so we go back to the
1930s where Tom Hanks worked as a
jailer in the section of
sentenced to death while having a
urinary tract infection but as it is taken
Hanks is the best prison guard in the world.
universe and its companions are also
the best in the world
They spit on them, the meanders shit with sticks
never abuse their power all good
all people except Carlos A.
This is the most despicable guy in the
history of cinema god his most important act
It is despicable that the fear of the bald man
not for his most despicable act of
kill the mouse has waited
for their most despicable acts no
we put the wet leaves in the peeling
when they like it and it makes them turn on
fire chao is the most person
despicable who knows the routine of the
green mile fit completely when
A new inmate arrives, John Coffee.
kind of forged but black and big
a coffee
m
He is a normal guy like me with
the small difference that killed two
girls and who has powers has the power
to cure a urinary tract infection by touching
of the cock
[Music]
She's really happy, imagine what I can do.
bad
here
up to here
[Music]
with confinement in the power to revive
mice with mouths and the power to
inserting images finally seems not to
show him so can that he was not the one
who killed the girls but it was the
Sam Rockwell himself, Tongas, brings together
his friends and tells them to listen to the wife
The owner of the prison has a tumor in his
the brain I think john coffee the
can cure I know that the only tests
What I have is that he touched my cock and it
It was a urinary tract infection that got in
a mouse in his mouth and saved him but it is
enough for me and besides I'm a tom
Hanks never made a wrong decision
then nation' koffi takes it out of the
jail they take him to the lady's house
It is made for the lady and a pim-pam-pum
cures the tumor
It's that they are not long mosquitoes that
long always when he uses his powers
He saves it and puts it in Percy's
mouth to stop if he goes crazy kills Sam
Rockwell and was admitted to a
neuropsychiatric forever
The movie could have ended there but
not because they don't forget that John Coffee
He is sentenced to death and they have to
kill yes or yes even though he is innocent
and even though he has powers but
before dying they are and one last one from sega
without means it was weight
[Music]
And now I'm going to ask you the
most important question they asked him
in their lives if they were condemned to
death which movie would you choose to watch for
last time to ask now if the
execution and Tom Hanks of dying or being
dear for the last time
as new
[Music]
the ice table
or not
this is deadly
[Music]
in the 70s a guy without talent
no grace writes a movie and without
whim to star in it as it was a
success was followed by a few sequels
Many years later those films
They are still a classic and people
He started to say the action that I do
here because in summary everything that happens to you
with the summary of the doc and well here
is today understand summarizes so that more the
Rocky saga this is the story of
Italian seedling Rocky Balboa un
middle-class boxer who in that
apartment talks to turtles
They worked for a mobster and on top of that all the
they treat it badly
If Rocky's life is a Picasso and
I need a hit then to get out
forward and they have that blow
roque one because apollo cred one
boxer who is the world champion
millionaire and successful and having a
fight with a rookie to get on his good side
its audience and all the newbies who
USA
right to roque
This is how Rocky prepares for the
fight of his life but obviously in
remain alone in your adventure accompany you
a modest cast of characters
secondary
perhaps millions of comedians like Adrian the
fat as rock's best friend is
nervous like the old rock boss
as the rock coach and the
special share of grass
All of them will help you prepare
for the big fight but before that we have
that is going to be boring but essential
the love story between rocky and jarana
Rock and Adriana chatting about rock and beyond
great pass to rock already sailing skating
rock and rock drainage and beyond
grave saints you put she who gives him the
sufficient forces to face the
great to polo page but first we have to
see stallone displaying his
wide range of acting resources
rock lover face and the face
awkward rock and angry face
rock and the face that says you just woke me up
news from the world of rock and the face of
They're beating the shit out of me like Rocky and
also has another side of the toxic lip
but that is due to a birth problem
so we can't laugh at all of them
forms none of that prevents you from having the
most important fight of his life but
first we have to see the best assembly
training with the best music
to train
and with all that you are ready to go
confront the great Apollo creed the
fight is even which is surprising
everyone and after a long while they leave
the fifteen rounds and the fight ends
then they start giving him the stitches
but here you don't have to wait until
in the result because the medium as
He wanted to win humanity then
and things could have ended here
but continue and continue in Roquetas
This movie is the same as the previous one
-except car that is successful and Apollo
all the tamales
your face to face book facebook youtube
then I want rock revenge and
He doesn't want to fight anymore, he wants to continue
Living romantic moments with Adriana
as they had and roti getting married four years
not that buying a new house is a good idea
and I think having a child
Rocky also wants to follow us
dazzling with her acting skills
face of I'm getting married in red face
I'm arguing about my Moroccan wife
and the most emotional moment and therefore
fierce claude error
question of theft here you realize that
If you don't have a handle then accept it.
Apollo's revenge and that's how we have
a new training setup
and the second big fight begins again
Apollo count them and after recounting
create them with blows, little rock, the blow
final and wins for what ended up becoming
in the world champion
one thing could easily have
ended there but continued and continued with
rolling 3 if you thought it couldn't be done
the script of the 1st is more likely to be
They are wrong because this is more or less
just like the previous ones, what is more
millionaire and more successful still has
romantic moments with his wife that
is more damaged and better dressed
continues to teach acting classes with the
face of me they are varying the rock and the
load of me they are inaugurating a
Rocky statue and the study charge
reflecting on the benefit of your
consequence of rock
and even an inexplicable face of this
running rock and also starred
a new emotional and yet acted moment
worse than the previous one with this coach
today
Apollo who is no longer an enemy
They made friends and also train him to
confront the villain of this movie
the evil Mario Baracus a fighter
wild kancheli that defies rock and pop
the title and as you might expect there is
a new training setup
Thus comes the third great rice fight
Rock and Roll vs. Mario Barracuda and Again
I got caught by knockout and the thing
It could have ended there but it continued and
continued with roque 4 now things got
politics because the bad guy is Ivan Drogo
Soviet Union boxer who will make
everything becomes an analogy
cheap of the cold war the first in
to confront him is Apollo who wants
claim but Russian kills him ping
literally the field dies and it is like this
as we see the face of I'm going to avenge myself
rock friend and obviously we return to
watch a new training montage
but now in Russia
[Music]
then the big fight begins
of rock and rock and against Ivan Drogo and
Obviously this cold war is won by the
saints in the end requires a beautiful
speech on the ground and all of Russia
applaud and if we believed that the franchise
rock swollen for more we are
wrong because someone is
happens to do rock and 5 but we don't
Let us rejoice so much because in this fifth
Some wanted to try new things
They don't really work for you, there isn't one
experienced boxers road rock
and there are no romantic moments with the
own target is carried badly there is no time
emotional and but acted and there is no montage
The only thing that happens in training is
that I open that has a student who later
He abandons her and then comes back to bring her
sapiña with rocky in a mediocre fight
street what he earns but no longer us
It matters we are disappointed
[Music]
with rock in going up the stairs in
company of your child and with this flavor
the room ends bitterly
that is to say the film more but no longer
My eyes hurt now from so much rock
There is only one way to lift this
reason singing
[Music]
This strong sums them up just like that number
50 at some point the 51 destiny will come out
What do you want us to join and do it again?
in the suggestion committee a week
coming
A few years ago people were watching
The Simpsons or rather when suddenly
someone did what bad gröning should
been a while
and it was then that the world knew the
duo of interdimensional travelers
turbid of the animated world that is why today it
summarize if not more the adventures of Ricky
martin
[Applause]
[Music]
They live in a more or less Yankee reality
less as we know it, that of the Smiths
a typical family of the universe 137 years ago
which is formed by Jerry as the father
failed and characterless set as the
mother obsessed with earning respect
of his father abandoning Summer as the
troubled teenage daughter dies and
like the son with an incipient door and
Week Sanchez like a grandfather like yours
Old Sanchez spends his time drunk
making inventions in the garage and
traveling to other dimensions by opening
portals with a gun but the strange thing
starts now
So hold on to your ass because you don't
You have no idea of all the places to
those who can take that track ready
because the issue is not that there is another
reality is that there are many realities and
Each one has its own rhythm, its own mortis, Jerry.
and the rest but as the kings are the
most intelligent beings in the world
universe known to be known and known
again building his own world that is
calls the citadel and like the dead
They are the most impressionable beings
They know they spend their time there paying attention to them
for everything except this one which would be a mortem
to what he wants to do his thing without
no ritual breaks the balls
because the truth is this duo doesn't have one
very healthy relationship
But look, Carrick is so bitter that
has a hard time relating to him or her
anyone including your other self your ex
couple that is an entity of mind
collective rolls bodies or with the
president
ah
[Music]
hot issue every time it seems that
He wants it and sometimes it seems that he is used
more and so our protagonist is
They pass from one reality to another and another
and another until one day it rips for you
They die in a timeline because he
also the lugo
[Music]
protagonists
gay showed more no matter what issue
those who sow replace the dead
without the family knowing everything every time
more murky but although the family is
important are also important
friends like this cat-shaped guy
disgust yesterday or this type you share
bird perversion or this guy with a head
from Cereté James our piparo and it
better than leaving them with you is to arm yourself
interdimensional parties
in front of
from right to left from left to
all are minor offenses
It turns out that Ricky and his friends
They met in a band of rebels and
are still listed on the list of
terrorists of the most naughty people of the
universe the galactic federation when
This interplanetary state governed
for insects take them into account and load them
the haughty bird wedding party and
They take Rick prisoner to get him out
secret of interdimensional travel
and it's really hot, imagine if they get into it
in the mind so it escapes by changing
from the body of an ultra frequency
direct
[Music]
between the escapes he takes advantage to do
[ __ ] the little world of the citadel and of
the government also passed
Galactic Federation of Evaluating the
currency the one who deposited dollars will receive
dollars
question that the other ricky martin
rebuilt in his world where a mortis
and being president and achieving equality
between the Ruiz Forros and the Mortis
ningunha dos so they make their own
party and wins the elections although
be because far from being the benevolent
political leader who decides to do this is
nothing more and nothing less and nothing more than the
very death and evil and begins his
mandate eliminating all opposition
in the most dramatic city and for
all the better musicalized in the series
[Music]
but for now this does not affect our
Ricky Martin favorites that follow with
his adventures like the time he
They put a helmet on the family dog
to make it smarter and you end up
look at that tie and end up having the
to pet facts or like when you
grab this box that makes some bugs
that are called
and third in a problem and disappear
But since he is already an idiot, they can't
solve your problem and if they don't
can solve the problem can't
disappear and how they cannot disappear
the crazy insurance if you want to kill
all or like that return that death uses
a position of love to get up
life that he likes but converts everyone
in monsters or like when a head
giant forces the earth to participate
in an interplanetary triumph operation
or like when some parasites that
implant memories in the brain
they get into the house or like when Rick gets
transformed into a cucumber
because at this point anyone
thing is an excuse for them to have
some adventure or say catchy phrases
that cures
[Applause]
although sometimes not everything is fun and
Scatological humor also has dilemmas
moral philosophical as slavery to
subatomic level gender issue
alien or medical ethics and other times
They paint them to take things from a movie with a
Freddy Krueger mixed with Inception
a Jurassic Park of diseases
8 The Sect or a Post-Apocalyptic World
just more macs
but it's not all fun and games either.
family life because the parents of
Martino are having a good time
and the truth is that it doesn't help at all
even leads him to express his
feelings in the form of monsters and
they finally get divorced
a joke to sing to the girl is happy
one I'm not happy and I haven't been since
a long time ago
[Music]
Even if he doesn't like the Sanchez family
schmid remains together to face the
season 77
good night
[Music]
and
the same
[Music]